http://www.stmarysbank.com/nav/about-us/privacy-security-policy

skip to main content
Download the St Mary’s Bank app on Google Play..
Dismiss
Toggle navigation
Search for:
TruStage Insurance
Guaranteed Asset Protection Plus (GAP Plus)
Contact Us
Bank beyond with us.
Open your account online now.
Get rewarded for everyday purchases with our Visa Platinum® Rewards credit card.
If you’ve moved on from your old job, so should your 401k.
Your best defense against becoming a victim of fraud is education.
Prevent fraud and unauthorized payments with Positive Pay.
Privacy & Security Policy
Privacy and security are top priorities at St. Mary's Bank. We are committed to protecting the security and confidentiality of your information and use a combination of state-of-the-art technology and methods to help ensure that your online sessions are secure.
We value the trust you have placed in us, we respect your privacy and are committed to safeguarding your nonpublic personally identifiable information. Please read our complete Privacy Policy below.
View printable PDF version here.
Rev. 12/2010
FACTS
WHAT DOES ST. MARY'S BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security
Transaction history
Account Balances
Account Transactions
Payment History
Checking account information
When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons St. Mary's Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. - See more at: https://www.stmarysbank.com/nav/About-Us/Privacy-Security-Policy#sthash.Izu3NJx9.dpuf
Reason we can share your personal information
Does St. Mary's Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
Questions?
Call toll-free 1-888-786-2791 or go to www.stmarysbank.com
What we do
How does St. Mary's Bank protect my personal information?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
How does St. Mary's Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Give us your contact information
Apply for a loan
Make a wire transfer
Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include:
Financial companies such as: St. Mary's Title Services.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
St. Mary's Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies.
Privacy Model Disclosure
VMP® Bankers Systems™
Wolters Kluwer Financial Services © 201050%
PRIV-MODEL  8/1/2010
2010.3/2576    2619786-010
Become a Member
History
Our Story
TruStage Insurance
Guaranteed Asset Protection Plus (GAP-Plus)
Credit Disability and Credit Life Insurance
Fraud Prevention
Security Alerts
Security Tips
Checks/Mail Scams
E-mail Scams
Phone Scams
ATM/Debit Card Fraud
×
You are about to leave the St. Mary's Bank Website.
The site you have selected is an external one located on another server. St. Mary's Bank has no responsibility for any external website. It neither endorses the information, content, presentation, or accuracy, nor makes any warranties, express or implied, regarding the external site. Thank you for visiting St. Mary's Bank.
You will be automatically redirected in 15 seconds. You may also click here to continue.
Proceed
Cancel
